Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 57, folder: 8 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Lookout Annual Report, Publication (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Box: 57, folder: 9 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Selling Sears Values Internally, Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
    April 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Retailer and the U.S.A. Economic Evolution, Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The Retailer and the State, Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: The Story of Sears, Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Notice of Annual Meeting of Stockholders, Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: A Brief History of Origins and Development: Merchant to the Millions, Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: To: The Men and Women Considering a Career with Sears, Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: This is Sears, Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: General Bibliography for Sears, Roebuck and Company, Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Box: 57, folder: 10 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Handbook for Salespeople: Basic Training, Publication (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Handbook for Getting Acquainted With Sears: Retail Basic Training, Publication (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Handbook for Getting Acquainted with Sears: Parent Basic Training, Publication (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Handbook for Getting Acquainted With Sears: Parent Basic Training, Publication (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Sears National Personnel Department: Its Organization and Function, Publication (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Senior Reserve Group: Status Report, Publication (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Sears, Roebuck and Co. Supervisory Training Program, Publication (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Box: 57, folder: 11 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Sears: Parent News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 11)
    Nov/Dec 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Sears: Parent News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Sears: Parent News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 11)
    January/February 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Sears: Parent News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Sears: Parent News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Tower News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 11)
    March 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Tower News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Tower News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 11)
    April 1978. Item is in English.
- Box: 57, folder: 12 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Check List and Reserve Group Rating Report, Publication (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Box: 57, folder: 13 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Quick Facts Notebook for New Employees, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Sears and the College Man: an invitation to discuss career opportunities with Sears, Roebuck and Co., Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Quick Basic Facts: Mail Order Training, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Your Military Leave, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Sears and the College Graduate, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Sears and the College Graduate, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Getting Acquainted with Sears, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Handbook for Getting Acquainted with Sears: Parent Basic Training, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Reserve Group Record Card, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Box: 57, folder: 14 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Sears Foundation Merit Scholarship Program for sons and Daughters of Sears employes, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Group Life Insurance and Travel Accident Plans, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Group Hospital and Surgical Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Group Hospital and Surgical Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Group Hospital and Surgical Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Certificate of Group Hospital and Surgical Benefits, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Group Life Insurance and Travel Accident Plans, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Group Life Insurance and Travel Accident Plans, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Medical Coverage for Retirees Age 65 or Over, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Medical Coverage for Retirees and Dependents, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Medical Coverage for Retirees Under the Age of 65, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Medical Plan for Employes and Their Families, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: Medical Plan for Employes and Their Families, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: Group Life Insurance and Travel Accident Insurance, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: Sears Supplemental Pension Plan: Rules and Regulations and Trust Agreement, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: Retiree Group Hospital and Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 17: Retiree Group Hospital and Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: Your Military Leave, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 19: Your Military Leave, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 20: The Savings and Profit Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck and Co. Employes, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 21: The Savings and Profit Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck and Co. Employes: Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 22: The Savings and Profit Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck and Co. Employes: Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 23: Your Social Security Program, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 24: Better Protection for Group Life Insurance Members and Their Dependents, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 25: You and Sears, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 26: Planned Training for Retail, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 27: How College Applicants Evaluate Job Factors, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 28: The Supplemental Savings and Retirement Plan: A Summary of Important Features, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 29: The Supplemental Savings and Retirement Plan: A Summary of Important Features, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 30: Good News for Sears Employes, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 31: Quick Basic Facts Notebook, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 32: Better Selling, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Box: 57, folder: 15 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Sears Parent News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Sears 1968 Annual Report, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Pacific Coaster, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Sears Annual Report 1964, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Parent News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Sears, Roebuck and Co. Annual Report 1962, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: The Story of Sears, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Midwestern News Graphic, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
    March 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Sears News Graphic, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: The Story in Brief, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Sears 1968 Annual Report, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Tips on Buying Time, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Something worth RepeatingAlways, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 14: What the Year 1962 Meant to You and Your Company, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: Factors Influencing Employee Morale, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: ABC: Citizens in Urban Renewal, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 17: A Decade of Change, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
    January 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Sears Dixieland News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 19: Sears Southwesterner: The All Employes Territorial Newpaper, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
    December 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Fortune, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 21: Share Your Ideas, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Box: 57, folder: 16 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Turn Your Ideas Into Cash, Publication (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Turn Your Ideas Into Cash, Publication (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: This is My Suggestion, Publication (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Box: 57, folder: 17 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Youand the Seattle-First National Bank, Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Box: 57, folder: 18 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Statement of Secondary School Teachers Association, Publication (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Box: 57, folder: 19 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Learning the Facts of Life, Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Memoradum with Respect to Proposed Ostrander Bill, Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
- Box: 57, folder: 20 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Security First National News, Publication (Box 57, Folder 20)
    February 1962. Item is in English.
- Box: 57, folder: 21 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Seibeneer, Publication (Box 57, Folder 21)
    March 1951. Item is in English.
- Box: 57, folder: 22 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Constitution and By-Laws of the Seneca Falls Machine Employee's Association of Seneca Falls, New York, Publication (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Annual Report of the Toledo Labor--Management--Citizens Committee for 1962, Publication (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Seneca Falls Machine Employees' Association, Publication (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Box: 57, folder: 23 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: You and Sentry, Publication (Box 57, Folder 23)
- Box: 57, folder: 24 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Personnel Handbook, Publication (Box 57, Folder 24)
- Box: 57, folder: 25 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Background Information: The Shamrock Oil and Gas Corporation First National Building, Publication (Box 57, Folder 25)
- Box: 57, folder: 26 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Corrrespondence, Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
- Box: 57, folder: 27 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Application for Position, Publication (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Personnel Procedures, Publication (Box 57, Folder 27)
- Box: 57, folder: 28 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Contest Smashes Records, Publication (Box 57, Folder 28)
- Box: 57, folder: 29 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Shell Oil Company 1968 Annual Report, Publication (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Shell News Report to Employees 1968, Publication (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: The Round-Up, Publication (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: The Round-Up, Publication (Box 57, Folder 29)
    March 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Cost and Waste Saving Ideas, Publication (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Item 6: Public Relations Department, Publication (Box 57, Folder 29)
- Box: 57, folder: 30 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: 25-Years Service Awards, Publication (Box 57, Folder 30)
- Box: 57, folder: 31 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: It's Everybody's Job: A Pocket Guide for Employees, Publication (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: You've Got What It Takes: to build a solid future at Sheffield, Publication (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: Personnel Procedures, Publication (Box 57, Folder 31)
- Box: 57, folder: 32 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: To Our Office and Clerical Employees, Publication (Box 57, Folder 32)
- Box: 57, folder: 33 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Linking Farm and City to Serve You Better, Publication (Box 57, Folder 33)
- Box: 57, folder: 34 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Employees' Suggestion System: Handbook of Information, Publication (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Correspondance, Publication (Box 57, Folder 34)
- Box: 57, folder: 35 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: What Shell Means to You, Publication (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Opportunities with Shell for Engineers, Scientists, Business, and Liberal Arts Graduates, Publication (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Personnel and Industrial Relations Departments, Publication (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: What Shell Means to You, Publication (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Item 5: Personal Audit and Ready Reference--My Shell Benefits, Publication (Box 57, Folder 35)
- Box: 57, folder: 36 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Crossing Craft Lines Merging of Salaried Supervision, Publication (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Employee Counseling, Publication (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: Use of Private Automobiles, Publication (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Item 4: Meal Allowance (Salary Employees), Publication (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Item 5: Excessive Oil Company Profits?, Publication (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Item 6: Opportunities With Shell, Publication (Box 57, Folder 36)
- Box: 58, folder: 1 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Matters of Fact: The Latchstring is Out, Publication (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: List of Booklets and Material Sent to Library of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: College Recruitment Program, Publication (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Shell Service Pay Plan Effective September 1, 1961, Publication (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Box: 58, folder: 2 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A Current Look at Shell, Publication (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Management Organization, Publication (Box 58, Folder 2)
    September 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Statement by J. G. Jordan Vice-President--Marketing--Shell Oil Company, Publication (Box 58, Folder 2)
    April 13, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Excerpts From Proceedings of Roosevelt Committee Hearings, Publication (Box 58, Folder 2)
    April & May 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Division List, Publication (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Old Mac Driver Had A Car, In That Car He Put Some Gasthis is about the price that he-and you-pay for gasoline, Publication (Box 58, Folder 2)
    By John Earl Davis. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Management Organization Chart, Publication (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Shell Oil Company Management Organization Chart, Publication (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Why you can't get all the gasoline you want, Publication (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Box: 58, folder: 3 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Current Look at Shell, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Report to Employees on 1966, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Shell Oil Company 1966 Annual Report, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Shell Progress, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
    July-August 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Shell Oil Company: Annual Report for 1952, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: The Houston Pecten, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
    March 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Shell Tidings, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Ohio Observer, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Head Office Management Letter: Burns Urges API Memebers to Advance Best Interests of Industry, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Head Office Management Letter: Shell Acquires Louisiana Acerage, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
    February 26, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Head Office Management Letter: New EPON* Paving for Jet Runways, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
    January 7, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Shell Oil Company Annual Report 1958, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Catalog of Motion Pictures, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: News Servce for employee newspapers, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: The 1960 American Voter: Presidential Election Edition, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Competition and You, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Fruit of a Plotted Plant, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Shell Oil Company: Annual Report 1960, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Shell Oil Company: Annual Report 1961, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Shell News Report to Employees on 1961, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
    April 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Shell News: Shell Visits the U.N., Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
    May/June 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Shell Oil Company: Annual Report 1963, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: Matters of Fact: Solutions, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: A Share in America, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: 1971 Shell Oil Company Annual Report, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: Head Office Management Letter: Shell Oil Company Reports Earnings of $144,588,000, Record Revenue of $1,827,832,000, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Box: 58, folder: 4 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Shell Oil Company and Ten Unions, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Articles of Agreement between Sewaren Employees' Association and Shell Oil Company, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Shell Oil Company and Independent Alliance of Petroleum Employees, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Shell Oil Company, Wood River, Illinois, Refinery and Nine Unions, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    January 1, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: In the Matter of the Arbitration between Shell Oil Company and Sewaren Emp[loyees Association (Ind), Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: How to Have Better Employee Relations and Improved Handling of Grievances, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Articles of Agreement Between Sewaren Independent Petroleum Workers' Union and Shell Oil Company, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Articles of Agreement between Sewaren Employees' Association and Shell Oil Company, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    Effective May 1, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Agreement between Shell Oil Company, Wood River, Illinois, Refinery and Eleven Unions Affiliated with AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    Effective May 1, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Agreement between Shell Oil Company, Wood River, Illinois, Refinery and Eleven Unions Affiliated with AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Articles of Agreement between Sewaren Employees' Association and Shell Oil Company, Incorporated, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Agreement by and between Shell Oil Company, Incorporated East Products Pipe Line Division and Tri-State Petroleum Workers Union, Inc., Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Box: 58, folder: 5 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Story of Sherwin-Williams, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Box: 58, folder: 6 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: League Members Approve Settlement With Unions and Elect New Board of Directors, Publication (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Box: 58, folder: 7 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Information for New Employees, Publication (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Shwayder Brothers Provides You With a Free Pension Plan for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 58, Folder 7)
    December 31, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Personnel Forms, Publication (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Box: 58, folder: 8 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Samsonite News, Publication (Box 58, Folder 8)
    April 22, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Samsonite Searchlight, Publication (Box 58, Folder 8)
    September-October 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Samsonite Searchlight, Publication (Box 58, Folder 8)
    July-August 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Samsonite Searchlight, Publication (Box 58, Folder 8)
    Apriol 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Samsonite Searchlight, Publication (Box 58, Folder 8)
    December 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Memento of Your Tour Compliments of Samsonite Luggage, Publication (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Box: 58, folder: 9 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Shwayder's Anti-Recession Move, Publication (Box 58, Folder 9)
    March 30, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: History of Shwayder Brothers, Inc., Publication (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Guideposts: How The Golden Rule Built a Great Business, Publication (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Box: 58, folder: 10 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Forms, Publication (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Box: 58, folder: 11 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: John W. Leslie, Publication (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Box: 58, folder: 12 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws of the Bulk Distribution Plant Employees' Union, Publication (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Box: 58, folder: 13 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Annual Report for 1965, Publication (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: The Singer Company Annual Report for 1964, Publication (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Box: 58, folder: 14 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Smith College Employees' Handbook for nonacademic employees, Publication (Box 58, Folder 14)
    Revised 1967. Item is in English.
- Box: 58, folder: 15 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: SCM Union Vote May Draw 4,250, Publication (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Box: 58, folder: 16 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Welcome to SKF, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Development Programs for Liberal Arts and Business Administration Graduates, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Smith Kline & French Laboratories: a growing company in the service of medicine, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Careers in Science atSmith Kline & French Laboritories, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Careers in Science at Smith Kilne & French Laboratories, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Welcome to SK&F, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Opportunities for Pharmacists in Industry, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
    By Rudolph H. blythe. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Professional Service Representative Employment Application, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: Employment Application, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: Employment Application, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Item 11: Personnel Procedures, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: Employee Agreement, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Item 13: Supervisor's Manual, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Box: 58, folder: 17 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Smith Kline & French Laboritories: Annual Report 1966, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: SK&F News, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
    December 22, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Smith Kilen & French, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: SKF's Compete is Complete!, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: SK&F Films Available for Community Audiences, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: How to Write to Senators and Congressmen, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: SK&F News Supplement, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
    October 20, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Smith Kline & French Foundation, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Letter to Employees, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
    June 5, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Smith Kline & French Laboratories Speakers Bureau, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: SK&F News, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
    April 2, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Catalog of Services, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Item 13: SK&F News, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
    April 16, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: SK&F News, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
    April 20, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: News Release, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
    March 2, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: News Release, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
    April 1, 1965. Item is in English.